《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
利维  找到能接替伊桑的人恐怕还要几周
Livy, it could take weeks to find Ethan's replacement.
在这段时间里  我还需要一个代理参谋长
In the meantime, I'm going to need a provisional chief of staff.
我想任命你
I would like that to be you.
拉里·莫斯想跟您通话
I have Larry Moss calling for you.
总统阁下  我们有证据表明
Ma'am, we have evidence
朱玛允许斯塔克伍德把桑加拉
Juma allowed Starkwood to use
作为制造生化武器的实验基地
Sangala as a base to manufacture biological weapons.
你是说这些武器就在美国本土吗
Are you saying these weapons are on us soil?
我们猜测这些武器就在
We suspect they're at the Starkwood headquarters
斯塔克伍德的弗吉尼亚总部
In Virginia.
你该不会是认为斯塔克伍德
And you're not suggesting that Starkwood intends
会使用这些武器来攻击我们的国家吗
To use those weapons to attack this country?
照他们今天的行动来看
Given their actions today,
我们必须马上对斯塔克伍德采取措施
We need to move on Starkwood immediately.
他们快杀将过来了
They're coming.
而且会拿着所掌握的证据找上门来
And they'll be coming with everything they've got.
唯一能制止他们的办法
And the only thing that's going to stop them
就是部署好这些武器
Is getting these weapons ready to deploy.
告诉我联邦调查局掌握了多少我们的情况
Tell me what the FBI knows.
我什么也不知道
I don't know anything,
霍奇斯先生
Mr. Hodges.
把他带出去
Get him out of here
该用刑时就用刑
And do what you have to do.
我不想因为乔纳斯·霍奇斯的疯狂行为
I'm not spending the rest of my life
而在监狱里过下半辈子
In prison because Jonas Hodges has lost his mind.
-你知道武器在哪里吗  -是的
- You know where the weapons are? - Yes.
杰克在哪
Where's Jack?
他试图保护武器不被夺走
He managed to secure the weapons,
但还是被斯塔克伍德抢了回去
But Starkwood got him back.
杰克暴露在毒气中
Jack was exposed.
但你们一定有办法可以救他
There has to be something that you can do to help him.
无药可医
There's no cure.
我们知道武器的方位了
We got a location on the weapon.
我们正准备派部队进行突袭
We're getting ready to stage a raid on the compound
我要参加
I want to go.
很抱歉  我不会批准
I'm sorry. i can't allow it.
我是唯一见过毒气罐的人
I'm the only one who's seen the canisters.
我知道它什么样
I know exactly what we're looking for.
但你被感染了  我们不知道
But you're sick. we have no idea
你什么时候会发作
When you're going to start showing symptoms.
你是对的
You're right.
武器到底在哪里
Where are the damn weapons?!
他耍了我
He played me.
西顿老弟给我们争取到了一点时间
Little old Seaton bought us some time.
我们要在整个基地中
We're going to do a point by point search of this entire compound.
做地毯式搜查
Of this entire compound.
这里有生化武器
There are biological weapons on this facility.
找不到  我们不会走
We're not going anywhere without them.
如果你们再得寸进尺
You try to advance any farther,
我们会开枪还击
You will be fired upon.
以下情节发生在凌晨12点至1点间
The following takes place between 12 a.m. and 1 a.m.
我数了下至少有三个排的兵力
I count three platoons at least.
全副武装
Everything mil-spec.
对  他们这是守株待兔
Yeah. they were waiting for us.
这是个大陷阱
This was one big trap.
蕾妮  用监控卫星帮帮我们
Renee, we would really use those satellite overheads.
收到  拉里
Copy, Larry.
-有进展没  -没有
- What have we got? - Nothing.
子网已经崩溃了
The subnet's been crashing.
等一下  等等  好了
Okay, wait, wait, wait. here we go.
我已重新连上5号卫星
I've got sat five retasting now...
谁能告诉我
Somebody talk to me.
你们都看见什么了
What are you seeing?
拉里  你们被四面包围了
Larry, you've got hostiles on all sides.
该死  给我找个突破口
Damn it. find me an opening.
正在找  但是没有能突围的路线
I'm looking, but there's no way through.
注意  大家都看见了吗
Okay, heads up. Is everybody seeing this?
拉里
Larry?
是的
Yeah.
我们看见了
Yeah. we're seeing it.
是霍奇斯
It's Hodges.
弟兄们听候您的差遣  先生
The men are at the ready, sir.
多谢您能亲自出马
I appreciate your presence.
那我还能去哪儿
Where else would i be?
谁是负责人
Who's in charge here?
我
I am.
我是莫斯探员
Agent Moss.
你得叫你的人退下  让我们继续搜查
You need to move your men and allow us to proceed.
我要你们离开我们的领地
I want you off our property.
还得把我的人放了
And i want you to release my man.
你们没权力把他扣为人质
You have no right to take him hostage.
我是奉美国总统之令行事
I have an order from the president of the united states.
奉命来搜查这栋楼
To search this building.
找出那些莫须有的武器
For weapons that do not exist.
搜了吗
Have you looked?
有大规模杀伤性武器吗
Are there weapons of mass destruction?
有任何武器吗
Are there weapons of any kind?
到底有还是没有
Is there anything in here at all?!
莫斯探员
Agent Moss,
谁这么异想天开
Who dreamed up this charade?
报上名来
Give me a name.
我们得追究到底
Let's get to the bottom of this.
你想跟我谈  霍奇斯先生
You want to talk to me, Mr. Hodges?
就让你的人把枪都放下
Get these guns off my head.
被人拿枪指着头就受不了了吗
You think you have a gun at your head?
那我呢
You know what i've got?
大半夜的  美国政府兵临城下
I've got the United States government sending SWAT Teams
派来了特警队还有武装直升机
And attack helicopters in the middle of the night.
我可是为国效忠了整整30个春秋啊
I've got a government that i served faithfully for 30 years,
换来的却是  那些没种露出真实嘴脸的
Dreaming up bs accusations,
政客们编造出一系列莫须有的指控
So politicians too cowardly to show their faces,
葬送了我毕生的基业
Can dismantle my company.
这就是我得到的回报
That's what i've got.
给你5分钟时间
You've got five minutes
你和你的手下坐着这些直升机
To get these-these helicopters flying out of here
给我离开这儿
With all of you on board.
你不能这样
You don't want to do this.
就5分钟
Five minutes.
放了我的人
And i want my man back.
蕾妮  听见了吗
Renee, you get that?
我们听见了
Yeah, we did.
-有何良策  -就5分钟吗
- And what options do we have? - In five minutes?
我知道没时间调兵遣将作战术支援了
I know there's no time to bring in more tac support,
有别的路可走吗
So give me something else.
好吧  拉里  给我一点时间  等一下
All right, Larry, give me a second. stand by.
就是这个
That's it.
我要给你看点儿东西
I want to show you something.
霍奇斯只给我们5分钟撤离基地
Hodges just gave us five minutes to clear the base.
形势对我们不利  我们失去了制胜先机
We lost that situation. we were outmaneuvered
但是我想我找到了一个新突破口
But i think i found us a new way in.
看  这是迈尔参议员提供的文件
Look. these are senator Mayer's files.
道格拉斯·诺尔斯  斯塔克伍德的主席
This is Douglas Knowles. he's the chairman of Starkwood.
就是他协助参议员进行调查
He was actually helping the senator with the investigation.
是他暗中协助披露了公司内幕
He is the one who brokered the deal to open the company's books.
又一个内应吗  不是刚上过一回当吗
What, another insider? didn't we just get burned?
听着
Just listen.
诺尔斯为霍奇斯干了快20年了
Knowles was loyal to Hodges for almost 20 years.
现在他却秘密地协助
And now he's secretly helping the
参议员搞垮斯塔克伍德公司
senator take down the Starkwood.
他有顾虑
He's scared of something.
这家伙会帮上我们的
This man wants to help us.
值得一试
It's worth a shot.
好的  给他打电话
Yeah. make the call.
我是诺尔斯
Knowles.
诺尔斯先生  我是杰克·鲍尔
Mr. Knowles, my name is Jack Bauer.
我从迈尔参议员那得到了你的号码
I got your number from senator Mayer.
迈尔参议员已经死了
Senator Mayer is dead.
是的  我知道  他遇害时我和他在一起
Yes, sir, i know. i was with him when he was killed
他是被你们的人杀的
By one of your employees.
名字叫约翰·奎恩
A man named John Quinn.
你不知道我有多希望有人来找我
You have no idea how much i was hoping someone would call.
抱歉  先生  我不明白
I'm sorry, sir. i don't understand.
事态越发地失控了
Things are very out of control.
你知道基地上正发生的事吗
Are you aware of what's happening on your base?
我正看着呢
I'm watching it with my own eyes.
联邦调查局被牵制住了
The FBI is pinned down.
他们说是来找生化武器的
They say they're looking for bioweapons.
先生  乔纳斯·霍奇斯手上持有
Sir, Jonas Hodges is  in possession.
军用级生化武器
Of a military-grade bioweapon.
是朱玛将军在非洲研发的朊病毒变体
A prion variant developed in Africa with General Juma.
武器不在他们搜的地方
Well, it's not where they think it is.
那不过是个空的飞机库
They're all standing in front of an empty hangar.
调查局被一个叫西顿的人给摆了一道
The FBI was deliberately led to the wrong location
被他带入了错误的方位  但我向您保证
By a man named Seaton, but i promise you, sir,
武器就在你们的基地
The weapon is on your base.
我试图拦截毒气罐时被感染了
I was contaminated when trying to intercept the canisters.
大概90分钟前
They were ferried back to Starkwood
他们被运回斯塔克伍德公司了
Approximately 90 minutes ago.
90分钟前  乔纳斯刚向董事会
90 minutes ago Jonas was handing down
宣布了他的全新战略
His new strategy to the board.
抵制政府  决不合作
Stonewall the government, no cooperation whatsoever.
难以置信会有这种事情发生
I can't believe this is happening.
先生  木已成舟
Sir, this is happening.
我发誓武器就在你们的基地
And i promise you the weapons are on your base.
你是否知道武器可能所在的位置
Do you have any idea where they might be?
我想我可能知道
I think i might.
诺尔斯先生  我要你
Mr. Knowles, i want to put you
跟我们在现场的一个外勤探员联系
in touch with one of my men in the field.
-能再打给你吗  -好的
- Can i call you right back? - Yes.
谢谢  走
Thank you. go.
有些弟兄不乐意招惹联邦探员
Some of the men were unhappy drawing down on federal agents.
可以理解
It's understandable.
我本就不希望拉普通士兵入伙
I had hoped not to include the rank and file.
他们靠得住的
You can count on them.
该下逐客令了
Let's show our guests the door.
行动
Let's move!
各就各位
Into position.
杰克  我耳机开了
Jack, i'm on comm.
我和沃克探员跟你通话
You're on with me and agent Walker.
霍奇斯的人开始重新部署了
Hodges' men have repositioned themselves.
好吧  我们动作要快点儿
Okay, we're going to have to move fast.
拉里  我要你和你的人
Larry, i want you and your men
佯装按霍奇斯的意思准时撤兵
To pull out on Hodges' timetable.
托尼  你想办法潜伏下来
Tony, you're going to need to find a way to stay behind.
我们要通过无线电让你
We're going to get your vectors
跟一个斯塔克伍德内部人士取得联系
over to a man that we contact inside Starkwood.
他叫道格拉斯·诺尔斯
His name is Douglas Knowles.
他知道武器藏在哪里
He believes he knows where the weapons are.
刚才不就是这么掉进陷阱的吗
Isn't this how we got into this mess?
阿尔梅达和某个貌似友好的内应
Almeida and some supposedly friendly contact?
诺尔斯是斯塔克伍德公司的主席
Knowles is chairman
他曾经协助参议员迈尔
Of the Starkwood board, but he was cooperating
调查斯塔克伍德公司
With senator Mayer's investigation of the company.
拉里  我们全靠他了
Larry, he is all that we've got.
我这有200双训练有素的眼睛盯着我呢
All right, i got 400 eyeballs trained on me right now.
怎么才能让阿尔梅达潜伏下来啊
How the hell are we supposed to get Almeida to stay behind?
拉里  你带着手下分散他们的注意力
Larry, i need you and your men to create a diversion
掩护托尼撤退
To cover Tony's escape.
听着  成败在此一举
Look, we need to make this work.
要是你们全都上了直升机
If you all get on those helicopters together,
咱们就永远失去夺回武器的机会了
We are going to lose this weapon for good.
拉里  你同意吗
Larry, are you on board with this?
我们得撤了
We got to go.
拉里  告诉我们  你同意不
Larry, we need to know, are you on board?
我尽力而为吧
I'll do what i can.
拿上他的包
Take his bag.
好了  我们走
All right, let's go.
我们撤退  你跟我走
We're standing down. you're coming with me.
等等
Hey, wait a minute.
协议里面没这项
This wasn't part of the deal.
什么协议  就我所知  不管怎样
What deal? As far as I could tell,
-他都不会管你的  -莫斯
- he couldn't care about you，one way or the other. - Moss.
把我的手铐打开
You take these handcuffs off of me
不然事情会越发不可收拾
Or it's going to get really ugly.
兄弟住手
Soldier!
滚吧  莫斯
Get the hell out of here, Moss.
别考验我们的耐心
You don't want to test us.
我们走
Let's go!
-不许动  -别开枪
- Don't move.  - No!
我是道格·诺尔斯
Doug Knowles.
-杰克·鲍尔叫我来的  -快过来
- Jack Bauer sent me.- Come on.
那条街上有监控摄像头
That street has security cameras.
现在带你去个禁区
I'll take you to a restricted area.
就在东区
It's on the east perimeter.
武器很有可能在那里
There's a good chance the weapons are there.
这里到处是巡逻兵
The place is crawling.
不知道我们怎样才能过去
I don't know how we're going to make it.
交给我吧
I'll take care of that.
杰克  我和诺尔斯接上头了
Jack, I'm with Knowles.
我需要东区的卫星图像支援
I'm going to need satellite support on the east perimeter.
杰克  我需要协助  听到没
Jack, I need support. do you copy?
杰克  蕾妮  能听到么
Jack, Renee, anybody
收到  托尼
Copy, Tony.
好  开始吧
Come on, let's go.
你们刚刚离开停机坪
I've got you just off the landing pad.
附近没有敌人
No hostiles in your immediate vicinity.
谨慎前进
Proceed at your own discretion.
收到
Copy that.
哪边
Which way?
杰克
Jack.
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
托尼和诺尔斯接上头了  一切正常
Tony and Knowles have connected. We're good.
该向白宫汇报进展了
It's time to call the White House with an update.
好的  我一会就去
Okay, good. I'll be right there.
总统阁下  抱歉打断你们的谈话
Madam President, excuse the interruption.
杰克·鲍尔在7号线上
Jack Bauer is on line seven.
鲍尔先生  告诉我你拿到生化武器了
Mr. Bauer, tell me you have the bioweapon.
总统阁下  恐怕进展不尽如人意
Madam President, I'm afraid that's not the case.
搜查被斯塔克伍德基地的
Our search was stopped by armed mercenaries
武装雇佣军阻止了
On Starkwood's base.
莫斯探员和他的手下被迫
Agent Moss and his men were forced to withdraw
从一场必败的战斗中退了回来
From a firefight they most certainly would have lost.
你是说霍奇斯的手下准备
Are you saying Hodges’ men were ready to fire
向联邦探员开火吗
On federal agents?
是的  总统阁下
Yes, ma'am, that's correct.
天哪
My god!
真是胆大包天
Who does he think he is?!
总统阁下  尽管我们行动受挫
Madam President, despite the setback,
但我确信武器还在那里
I am confident the weapons are still there.
我已联系斯塔克伍德的主席
I reached out to Starkwood's chairman.
他愿意合作  正和托尼·阿尔梅达在一起
He's willing to cooperate. He's with Tony Alameida now.
他们正赶往基地的安全区
They are moving towards a secure area on the base
我们相信武器就藏在那里
Where we believe the weapons are being held.
非常好
Very good.
蒂姆  部队现在什么情况
Tim, what's our troop status?
正在调遣
Mobilizing.
国防部长说
The Secretary of Defense says
他们还要几个小时
They're still several hours out.
现在大战在即
At which point we have a war on our hands
我们要对付的是1500名
Against 1,500 mercenaries
装备了生化武器的雇佣兵
Armed with bioweapons.
总统阁下  我相信
Madam President, I do believe that
只要能确定武器的精确位置
a surgical air strike will work as long as
发动迅猛的空袭必能奏效
we can pinpoint the exact location of the weapon.
你能做到吗
And you can do that?
是的  我相信我们能
Yes, I believe we can.
鲍尔先生  你看过
Mr. Bauer, you've seen the canisters
装生化武器的罐子
Containing the bioweapons, you know what
你知道它们的样子吧
They look like, is that correct?
是的  总统阁下
Yes, ma'am.
一旦阿尔梅达找到毒气罐
Then we'll need you to verify the canisters
需要你去核实
Once Almeida has located them.
不得有误
No more mistakes.
鲍尔  我们需要你亲眼验证
We're gonna need visual confirmation from you, Bauer-- eyes on.
杰克  这一环节不容出现任何差池
Jack, we have got to get this part right.
了解  还有什么吩咐吗
I understand. anything else?
杰克  我听说你被病原体感染了
Jack, I have been told that you were exposed to the pathogen.
你现在怎样
How you doing?
现在我很好  总统阁下
Right now I'm fine, Madam President.
谢谢您的问候
Thank you for asking.
感谢你为国家做出的贡献
Thank you for your service.
我不会让你就这样死去的
I'm not giving up on you.
有事随时通知我
Keep me informed.
好  总统阁下
Yes, ma'am.
走吧
Let's go.
我现在很忙
I don't have a lot of time.
怎么了
What's going on?
我还要问你怎么了呢
That's what i've been trying to ask you.
我打了三次电话
I called three times.
我现在快忙死了
It's kind of crazy here right now.
除非你有急事  我等会再打给你
Unless it's urgent, I gotta call you back.
我听说召开了参谋长联席会议
I'm hearing rumors that the joint chiefs have been called in.
没什么大事
It's not a big deal.
他们只是在降低警报等级前
They're just doing a final assessment
做最后评估
Before lowering the alert level.
奥利维亚  别来这套
Olivia, don't do this.
什么
What?
我说的是实话啊
I'm telling you the truth.
是吗
Really?
港务局集装箱堆积场的线人
Because I've got a source in the port authority
说的是大规模杀伤性武器
Container yard who's using terms like "weapons of mass destruction,"
自然我就会想
so naturally I'm wondering
这就是召开参谋长联席会议的原因吧
If that's why the joint chiefs are having a meeting.
听着  我对此无可奉告
Look, I can't talk about it.
这关系到国家安全
It's obviously a question of national security.
但我保证  我会第一时间告诉你
But you have my word I'll tell you soon as I can.
我现在就想知道
I want to know now.
肯  我可刚给了你一条爆炸性新闻
I just gave you a big story, Ken.
这次你得等了  我要挂了
You'll have to wait. I gotta go.
奥利维亚  别挂
Don't hang up on me, Olivia.
否则你会后悔莫及
That'd be a big mistake.
你什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
好吧  这可是你逼我说的
You want me to say it, fine, I'll say it.
想想吧  要是你妈知道
Think how your mother would feel when she hears
是你逼走她的参谋长
That you forced out her chief of staff
而取而代之  她会作何感想
So you could take over his position.
是他自己无能
He was incompetent.
但早报不会这么写
Yeah, well, it won't play that way on the morning news.
还是对我实话实说吧
So, talk to me.
就现在
Now.
我不能在这告诉你
I can't talk here.
我在罗斯福大陆酒店1271房间
I'm in the Roosevelt Continental, room 1271.
给你半小时时间
You've got half an hour.
皮尔斯探员  请给我备辆车
Agent Pierce, please get a car ready.
我有急事
I have to make a quick run.
杰克  我们到了
All right, Jack, we're here.
诺尔斯说这几天
Knowles says there's been increased activity
这片区域内活动频繁
In this area for several days now.
我看了约6栋建筑
I'm looking at about a half a dozen buildings.
每栋都有可能
Could be any one of them.
收到  托尼
Copy that, Tony.
别挂  红外线扫描中
Hold on, we're getting infrared up now.
我看到在你附近有7栋建筑
I'm counting seven buildings in your immediate vicinity.
你的正东南方向的建筑
The building directly southeast of your current
没有显示红外信号
Position is showing no infrared signal.
可能被屏蔽了
I'm guessing they're using a blackout shield.
好的  我们先去那看看
All right, we'll try there first.
路上有没有巡逻的
You see any patrols coming our way?
没有  很安全
Negative, you're clear.
好的  走吧
Okay, let's go.
杰克  诺尔斯的钥匙卡开不了门
Jack, Knowles' key card isn't working.
需要电子支持
We're gonna need electronic support here.
在你的通信装置背面
There should be an R-6 interface module
应该有个R-6接口模件
On the back of your comm device.
我知道那是什么  谢谢
Yeah, I know what that is, thank you.
我插进去了
I'm plugging in now.
好  开始
Okay, we're up.
是库马克Z系列
Cormac z series.
我们在解密5位数的电子钥匙
We're looking at a five digit key
它受高标加密模式下的分组密码保护
Protected by an AES block cipher.
正在解码
Running combinations.
托尼  有辆车正向你方驶来
Okay, Tony, you've got a vehicle coming your way.
在你东侧距离约100码
It's east of you about a hundred yards.
到下面找掩护
Take cover down there.
还有多久
How much longer?
你还需要多久
How much more time do you need?
5个数字才解出2个
I only have two out of five digits.
我们在这里完全无法隐蔽
We're pretty exposed here.
杰克
Jack?
我没事
It's all right, I'm fine.
快
Come on.
趴下
Stand down.
托尼  还差2个数字
Two more numbers, Tony.
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
还差2个数没解出
We still got two digits to go.
靠近看看
Move in for a closer look.
我们躲不过了
We are not gonna make it.
待在这别动
Sit tight.
道格  你去哪  道格
Doug, where you-- Doug!
站住别动
Hold your position.
让我看看证件
May I see some ID?
道格·诺尔斯
Doug Knowles.
糟了
Dame it.
还差1个
One to go.
抱歉  诺尔斯先生
I apologize, Mr. Knowles.
霍奇斯先生已经下令
Mr. Hodges has ordered the base
本基地所有无关人员不得擅闯
Cleared of all nonessential personnel.
无关人员
Nonessential personnel?
我是董事会主席
I'm chairman of the board.
我理解  可我们正处在高度戒备状态
I realize that, but we're dealing with a heightened security situation here.
所以我要知道您来这有何贵干
So, I need to know what you were doing in this area.
乔纳斯深夜召开董事会
Jonas called a late night board meeting,
所以我出现在这里
that's what I'm doing here.
先生  那会议12小时前就散了
Sir, that meeting ended nearly 12 hours ago.
完成  可以进去了
We got it; we're in.
我无须向你解释
I don't have to explain myself to you, you know.
抱歉  先生  可你必须解释
I'm sorry, sir, but you do.
先生  我想你没听懂我的话
Sir, I don't believe you're hearing me.
不  是你没有听懂我的话
No, I don't think you're hearing me!
是我建立了这家公司
I built this company!
不需要你来教我
And I don't need you telling me
我该去哪儿不该去哪儿
Where I can and cannot walk!
明白吗
Understood?!
先生  你得和我们走一趟
You're gonna have to come with me, sir.
这边走
Right this way.
我进来了
I'm in.
可他们带走了诺尔斯
But they got Knowles.
你觉得他会走漏消息吗
Do you think he's gonna say anything?
不清楚
I don't know.
不过我最好快进快出
But I better get in and out as fast as possible,
以防他泄露消息
just in case he does.
托尼  总统需要
Okay, Tony, the president needs a visual
在发动攻击前亲眼看到武器
On the weapons before she'll launch an attack.
她需要你亲眼看到毒气罐
She needs your eyes on the canisters
然后由杰克确认
and a confirmation by Jack.
收到
Copy that.
很好
Good.
杰克
Jack?
待在这  我马上回来
Stay here, i'll be right back.
杰克  杰克
Jack! Jack?!
杰克
Jack!
Jack?!
杰克
Jack?
叫医护人员来
Get me the medic!
是  长官
Yes, sir.
我们刚发现诺尔斯先生一个人
We just found Mr. Knowles alone,
在禁区外面
Just outside the restricted zone.
他有合理解释吗
Did he have an explanation?
是的  长官  他说他在散步
Yes, sir, he said he was walking.
散步
Walking.
要把他带到斯多克斯那里接受审问吗
Should i take him to stokes for interrogation, sir?
兄弟  你是在建议我们把他五花大绑
You're suggesting what, soldier, that we strap him down,
逼他招供  就因为他在散步
Extract a confession, because he was walking?
他是董事会主席
He's the chairman of the board.
长官  我只是在请求指示
I was just requesting instructions, sir.
您要我怎么做
What you'd like done.
我要你把他带到他的办公室
I'd like you to take him to his office.
让他舒舒服服的
Make sure he's comfortable.
然后盯着他直到我过来
And stay with him until i arrive.
明白  长官
Yes, sir.
还有其他指示吗
Will that be all?
打给第9区
Call zone nine,
叫他们增加安检
Have them double down security.
我们得确认诺尔斯先生是一个人
Let's make sure that Mr. Knowles was in fact alone.
明白  长官
Yes, sir.
还要多久
How much longer?
半小时
Half an hour.
很好
Good.
完成后马上通知我
I'll need to know the minute it's done.
好的  长官
Yes, sir.
亚伦  可以的话你能在大厅等我吗
Aaron, i'd like you to wait in the hall, if that's okay.
泰勒女士  您让我负责您的安全
Ms. taylor, you tasked me with handling your security.
我不能让您进入
I can't allow you to enter a hotel room
我没有检查过的酒店房间
I haven't vetted.
亚伦  感谢你的关心
Aaron, i appreciate the concern.
但你从这里就能看见房门
But you can see the door from here,
我也设了快速拨号
I have you on speed-dial,
如果真有什么事  我会大声呼救的
And i can scream very loudly when the occasion demands.
我只需要两分钟去说服一个记者
I just need two minutes to wrangle a reporter.
真的  我不会有事的
Really, i'll be fine.
好吧  如有需要  我马上过来
All right, i'll be here if you need me.
-想喝点什么  -不用了
- Want a drink? - No.
我想你应该不介意我喝点儿吧
I assume you don't mind if i do.
漫长的一天
It's been a day.
我得告诉你
I gotta tell you.
我不喜欢别人威胁我
I don't like being threatened.
我知道不合适宜
It was unfortunate.
我道歉
I apologize.
肯  我们是老相识了
We've known each other a long time, Ken.
我本以为我们已经达成一项共识
I thought we had an understanding.
是达成了
We do.
我也很想继续这样
And i want to keep it that way.
我们俩都这么想的  对吗
We both do. am i right?
好吧  我跟你说过  我收到线报
Okay, so, i told you, i have this source.
线人是港务局集装箱堆积场的警察
Cop,out at the port authority container yard.
嗯
Okay.
他跟我说他看见一些貌似职业杀手的人
He told me he saw these professional assassin types
几个小时前在那里激烈交火
Get into an intense firefight out there a couple hours ago.
据他讲  有人劫持了一批大规模杀伤性武器
According to him, someone hiJacked a WMD
不知道要运往何处
out to god knows where.
是这样
That's true.
是吗
Yeah.
我想知道所有情况
Yeah, i want to know all about it.
如果你觉得你只需要点点头
Look, if you think all you've got to do is nod your head
来确认我已经知道的消息  那是不行的
Confirming what i already know, then we've got a problem.
事关国家安全  肯
It's national security, Ken.
我无可奉告
I can't tell you.
我说你可以
I'm saying you can.
如果这个消息外传  会造成恐慌
If this story breaks, it would create a panic.
人们会受到伤害
People would be hurt.
如果你知道内情  你就会明白
If you knew what it was, you'd understand why
为什么要严格保密了
It's got to stay a secret.
没错  就是这样  我会理解的
Right, exactly. i'd understand.
相信我  好吗
Have a little faith, okay?
好吧  在集装箱堆积场里有生化武器
All right. there is a bioweapon in the container yard.
那群人就是在争夺这个东西
That's what they were fighting over.
它是由斯塔克伍德在非洲研制的
It was developed by Starkwood in Africa.
-斯塔克伍德  -没错
- Starkwood? - Right.
他们已将武器运到离这里30英里的基地
They moved it to their base about 30 miles from here.
这么说武器现在就在那里了
So it's there right now.
这就是联席参谋长会议讨论对策的主题
So this is what the joint chiefs are discussing, what to do about that.
奥利维亚
Olivia...
总统已下令  一旦发现毒气罐的位置
The president ordered an air strike
就马上进行空中打击
As soon as the exact location of the canisters was known.
现在你明白为什么不能报导此事了吧
So you see why you can't run with this?
真的  肯  你不能报导的
Really, Ken, you can't.
很多人的生命岌岌可危
A lot of lives are at stake.
整个计划成功的关键就在于奇袭
The entire plan depends on surprise.
你明白的  对吧
You get that, right?
也许你是对的
Maybe you're right.
也许我不应该报导
Maybe i need to kill this story.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的意思是  也许应该有人来说服我
What i mean is maybe somebody could convince me.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
你知道我的意思
You know what i'm saying.
你发扬爱国精神的时候  真的很美
You're very beautiful when you get all patriotic.
我有跟你说过吗
I ever tell you that?
我们已经结束了  我们都同意了
That's over. we agreed.
是你一厢情愿
You agreed.
真的  我不想这样
Really, i don't want to do this.
肯
Ken...
那就拒绝我吧
Then say no.
这是盘多帕敏  能控制发抖的症状
This is Pandopamine which should control the shaking.
按住
Here, apply pressure.
你可以每隔两小时  注射一次
You can give yourself an injection once every two hours.
如有需要  可增加次数
More if needed.
你觉得我会需要更多的注射吗
You think i'll need more?
十有八九  是的
In all likelihood, yes.
在接触生化剂后这么快就出现症状
The onset of symptoms so soon after exposure suggests
说明生化剂比我们想的要厉害得多
The bio-agent is more virulent than we thought.
我们所做的只是控制症状而已
All we're doing here is just masking the symptoms.
我明白
I understand.
不过有件事你也许会考虑一下
There's something you may want to consider, though.
什么事
What's that?
布莱登大学一直资助朊病毒疾病的研究
Bryden University has been funding some studies on prion diseases.
该研究目前尚处试验阶段
The work is purely experimental at this point,
但它的确提出了治疗方法
but it does suggest treatment.
这是好消息啊
That's good news.
我不想让你们抱太大希望
I don't want to get anyone's hopes up here.
因为治愈的几率很小
We're talking a slight chance.
治疗方法采用干细胞
A possible treatment using stem cells
需从基因匹配的捐赠者身上提取
From a genetically compatible donor.
直系亲属是最好的捐赠人选
An immediate family member would make the best donor candidate.
我看了你的档案
I saw your file.
你有个女儿  对吧
It says you have a daughter, right?
我不想让我的女儿牵涉进来
I don't want my daughter involved in this.
-杰克  如果真有机会治疗  -鲍尔先生
- Jack, if there's a chance. - Mr. Bauer...
医生  谢谢你所做的一切
Doctor, thank you for everything you've done.
抱歉  我得回去做事了
Excuse me. i need to get back to work.
杰克
Jack...
这不关你的事
This is none of your business.
你在调查局里病情发作
It's my business when you're having a seizure
-这就关我的事  -你听到医生的话了
- In the middle of the FBI. - You heard the doctor.
治疗只是抑制了病症
The medication will mask the symptoms.
你为什么就不愿意谈一下呢
Why won't you even talk about this?
-谈什么  -实验治疗疗程
- Talk about what? - The experimental procedure.
因为没什么好谈的
Because there's nothing to talk about.
她是你女儿  你难道不打算让她知道吗
She's your daughter, and you're not even gonna let her know?
对
That's right.
你甚至连试一试都不愿意吗
So you're just not even gonna try?
蕾妮  我知道你想帮我
Renee, i know you're trying to help,
但你不了解情况
But you don't know what you're talking about here.
我女儿跟我都不说话的  明白吗
My daughter and i, we don't talk, okay?
所以  请你不要再管了
So, please, just let it go.
这应该由她来决定
It should be her choice.
不是
Well, it's not.
我才是快死的那个  该由我来决定
I'm the one who's dying. it's my choice.
还没有发现目标  托尼正在寻找
No sign of the target yet, but Tony's working on it.
你看起来好多了
You look better.
谢谢
Thanks.
托尼  听得到吗
Tony, can you hear me?
杰克  你没事吧
Jack, you okay?
我没事
Yeah, i'm fine.
托尼  我们看到大楼外面有人来了
Okay, Tony, we're seeing new activity outside the building.
两辆车  8个敌人
Two vehicles, eight hostiles.
看起来像支安保小队
Looks like a security detail.
你觉得诺尔斯出卖他了吗
You think Knowles gave him up?
托尼  他们直奔你所在的入口了
Tony, they're moving straight for your point of entry.
8个敌人正向你方逼近
Eight hostiles and closing.
我听到他们的声音了
Yeah, i hear them.
你想要重新部署吗
You want to regroup?
不  我想赶快了结这件事
No, i want to get this over with.
安全  行动
Clear. Move.
安全  就是那里
Clear. Right there.
2号  3号  这里安全
Two three, we're clear.
我以前没在这见过你
I haven't seen you here before.
他们刚派了我们8个人过来
They just sent eight of us over here, sir.
为什么  出什么事了
Why, is something wrong?
没事  只是谨慎起见
No, sir. just, you know, precautions.
没错  没错  疑神疑鬼的还不够啊
Right, right. can't be paranoid enough.
我在主楼
I'm in the main building.
收到  我们看到你了
Copy, we're with you.
托尼  我是杰克
Tony, it's Jack.
你在平均海平面125英尺处
I've got you at 125 feet MSL,
大概是地下40英尺左右  对吗
Approximately 40 feet underground. is that correct?
对  我在地下四层
That's right. i'm four floors down.
关于那栋楼底下的情况
We've got no information on any kind of
我们一点信息都没有
subterranean floors in that building.
相信我  就在这里
Believe me, they're here.
环氧树脂加固墙  灌浇混凝土天花板
Epoxy-hardened walls, poured concrete ceilings.
我看见武器了
I have a visual on the weapon.
正发送图片给你们确认
Sending images for verification now.
收到
Copy that.
是毒气罐
Okay, those are the canisters.
我去通知史密斯上将
I'll notify Admiral Smith
目标已找到并确认
the target is located and confirmed.
托尼  那就是毒气罐
Tony, those are the canisters.
杰克  看起来他们
Jack, it looks like they're transferring
正把毒气罐里的病原体
The pathogens from the canisters
转移到某种传输系统里
Into some sort of delivery system.
正在运送
It's on the move.
收到  没关系
Copy that. it doesn't matter.
蕾妮正通过电话传送坐标
Renee's phoning in the coordinates.
十分钟后那里的一切就灰飞烟灭了
Everything's gonna be dust in the next ten minutes.
-马上离开  -收到
- Get out of there now. - Copy that.
正在撤退
Withdrawing.
好了  弟兄们
Okay, men.
乔纳斯  你怎么解释
You want to explain this, Jonas?
我被自己的安保人员拘捕
I'm arrested by our own security force.
像个犯人一样被关在自己的办公室里
Held captive in my own office like a prisoner.
甚至他们连我打电话给你
They won't allow me a phone call, even to you,
问问发生什么事了都不允许
To find out what the hell is going on!
抱怨还真不少呀  道格
Well, that's a lot of complaints, Doug.
说完了吗
You done?
你几个小时前就应该回家了
You were supposed to be home hours ago.
为什么有人看见你四处窥视呢
Why'd they find you snooping around?
我看到调查局突袭我们
I saw the FBI raid.
他们说我们持有生化武器
They say we have bioweapons.
他们根本没找到
Which they did not find.
那不是重点
That's not the point.
是真的吗
Is it true?
记得我20年前第一次带你来这吗
Remember when I first brought you out here 20 years ago?
这里空无一物
There was nothing here.
什么也没有
Nothing.
我们在这片土地上  白手起家
And out of the damn mud,
建立起这家公司
We built this place,
组建起西半球乃至全世界最大的私人军队
The largest private army in the hemisphere, maybe the world,
一次又一次地拯救美国人民
And we pulled America's ass out of the fire
于水火之中
Again and again and again.
回答我的问题
Answer the question!
我正在回答你
I am.
每一天  我们都在做一些政府
Every day, we've done things
不能或是不愿意做的烂事
That the government itself could not or would not do.
他们就会说
"get this done,"
做好这件事  这是你们的任务
That's what they said, "here's your mission."
根本没人过问这些都是怎么完成的
Nobody asked how anything was gonna be done.
没有人关心
Nobody wanted to know.
每个人要的只是结果  我们给他们了
All anyone wanted was results, and we delivered.
没有人怀疑这一点
No one's questioning that.
没人怀疑吗
No one's questioning that?
你不是疯了吧
You're not insane, are you?
参议院  委员会  总统
The senate, the committees, the president.
华盛顿每一个喋喋不休的废物
Every chattering nonentity in washington
总在那以那些个教条来吹毛求疵
Is out there with their standard operating procedures
说着  这怎么做的  那又是怎么做的
Saying, "how was this done? How was that done?"
每一个人都试图分裂我们  搞垮我们
Tearing at us, trying to bring us down, every one of them.
我使国家强盛安定
I kept this country strong. I kept it safe.
我不会为此而要受到迫害
And I will not be persecuted for that.
乔纳斯  你不能对本该
Jonas, you cannot start a war against the people
保护的民众发动战争
You're supposed to protect.
双方已经开战  道格
We were at war, Doug,
从他们决定要解散我们的那一刻起就是了
The moment they decided to dismantle us.
关于那个武器
And as for particular weapons,
关于你的那个问题  我换个方式问吧
As for your question, let me rephrase it.
我们准备好自卫反击了吗
Are we prepared to defend ourselves?
准备好了
We are.
乔纳斯
Jonas...
你不能和政府作对啊
You can't take on the federal government.
你从来就不是个从大处着想的人
Yeah, well, you never were one for thinking big.
20年来
20 years
我对你视如己出
I treated you like a son.
20年了
20 years.
你的那一点点忠心
A little loyalty...
我还是应得的吧
Wasn't that the least I deserved?
请讲
Yes.
我们有一个截击雷达系统发出警报
Sir, we just got an alert from one of our radar intercepts.
一支F-18飞行中队
There's a squadron of F-18's
从弗吉尼亚海滩向我方袭来
Heading our way out of Virginia beach.
先生
Sir?
什么时候到达
What's the ETA?
不到十分钟
Less than ten minutes.
-我们准备得怎么样了  -多少
- What's our readiness? - How many?
三个弹头已经装好
We have three loaded.
打电话给总统
Place the call to the president.
我马上就到
I'll be there momentarily.
你现在大概觉得我是世上最烂的人渣了
You probably think I'm the scum of the earth right now.
我只关心你别把斯塔克伍德的事报导出去
All I care about is that you don't run the Starkwood story.
你还真是精神可嘉
You're a real sport.
牺牲小我为大我
Taking one for the team like this.
看着我
Look at me.
你不会报导这件事的  对吧
You won't run it, right?
对不起  利维
I'm sorry, Livy.
什么
What?
我必须报导
I have to run it.
这么大的爆炸性新闻
Breaking something this big
会让我在纽约受万众瞩目
Will put me over the top in New York.
我保证没人会知道是你泄露的消息
I'll make sure nobody knows any of it came from you.
你这个撒谎的混蛋
You lying son of a bitch.
好了啦
Come on, please.
我所做的一切都是为了自己
I'm did what I needed to do
能飞黄腾达  就像你一样
to get ahead-- Just like you.
我们之间没有可比性
There's no comparison.
报导这件事会伤及整个国家
Running that story will harm the country.
我在华盛顿混的时间可比你长得多
I've been in Washington a lot longer than you.
你会明白  游戏就是这么玩的
You'll see, this is how the way the game is played.
肯  还是我教教你怎么玩吧
Actually, Ken, this is how the game is played.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你报导这件事  或以后再试图敲诈我
You run that story, or ever try to blackmail me again,
我就会让所有人都知道
And I'll make sure everyone knows
你是怎么得来的线索
Just how you get your leads.
我觉得你夫人会非常感兴趣
I think your wife will be especially interested.
从你告诉我的事情来看
From everything you've told me,
那会是非常令人不快的离婚
That's gonna be one nasty divorce.
贱人
You bitch
找条新路吧  肯
Find a new beat, Ken.
我不想在白宫附近再见到你
I don't want to see you around the White House again.
抱歉  我要接这个电话
Sorry, I've got to take this.
请讲
Hi.
你去哪了
Where in the world are you?
抱歉  我在K街有一个会面
I'm sorry. I had a meeting on K Street.
我必须要跟一个记者周旋
I had to run interference with a reporter.
媒体已经知道了吗
Are the press on to this?
没关系了  我搞定了
Not anymore. I took care of it.
我需要你  利维
I need you here, Livy.
我们有了生化武器存在的证据
We've had confirmation on the bioweapons,
现在正在施行空中打击
And the air strike is happening now.
五分钟后就到
I'll be there in five minutes.
上将  进展如何
Where are we, admiral?
F-18战斗机群已经装载上
The f-18's have been loaded with
激光制导掩体破坏弹
bunker-buster ordinance
7分钟之后便可到达射程
And will be in range in seven minutes.
病原体扩散到周边地区的几率有多大
What's the risk of the pathogen spreading to the surrounding areas?
最小限度
Minimal.
我们用的是磷弹
We're using white phosphorous charges,
燃烧时可达5000摄氏度
Which burn at 5,000 degrees.
绝对可以完全摧毁病原体
More than enough to incinerate the pathogen.
疾病控制中心确认这一点了吗
And that's been confirmed by the CDC.
是的
It has.
武器准备好了吗
Weapons are ready?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
给总统的电话呢
The call to the president?
正在打
The call is in process.
今天是个有历史意义的日子  先生们
It's an historic day, gentlemen.
对斯塔克伍德来说是个大日子
A great day for Starkwood.
遗憾的是诺尔斯不能和我们共襄盛举了
Too bad Mr. Knowles can't be joining us.
收到  请爬升到平均海平面9000英尺
Roger, I need 9,000 feet MSL
报告武器控制状态  完毕
and weapons control status, over.
武器控制状况  黄色警备
Weapon's control status,yellow tight.
战斗机进入打击范围内
Fighters entering the ip.
进入空域协调区
Engage airspace coordination area.
-收到  -待命
- Roger that. - stand by.
总统阁下  指挥控制中心报告
Madam president, command and control is reporting
有相位阵列雷达系统
That a phased array radar system
在斯塔克伍德基地附近运行
Is active inside the Starkwood compound.
什么意思
Meaning what exactly?
他们知道我们要来
They know we're coming.
有高射炮威胁的可能性吗
Is there any evidence of an antiaircraft artillery threat?
情报显示他们没有那种防空能力
Intelligence is indicating no such capability on the ground.
总统阁下  有您的电话
Madam president, there's a phone call for you.
是乔纳斯·霍奇斯打来的
It's Jonas Hodges.
接到免提上
Put him on speaker.
阁下  他要求跟您私下谈
Ma'am, he's requested a private conversation.
他说在中控室设了一条专线
He says he's established a proprietary line in the ops room.
专线
A proprietary line?
他是怎么办到的
How did he manage that?
我不清楚
I have no idea.
请讲
Hello.
总统阁下  走到今天这一步
Madam president, let me begin by saying
请先让我表示诚挚的歉意
That I am truly sorry it's come to this.
但我还得强烈要求您
But I have to insist
最好赶快召回您的战斗机
you turn your planes around immediately.
你没资格发最后通牒  霍奇斯先生
You're in no position to issue ultimatums, Mr. Hodges.
或许我有
Well, maybe I am.
总统阁下  记得几年前
You remember several years ago, Madam President,
斯塔克伍德驻扎在巴基斯坦
Starkwood was deployed to Pakistan.
印象深刻
Oh, I remember it very well.
我反对那次部署
I fought that deployment.
结果您输了
And you lost.
您应该也还记得
You'll also recall
那时我们征用过的导弹系统
That we requisitioned a missile system at that time--
巨蟒五号
Python fives.
三枚那样的导弹
Well, three of those missiles
现正装满病原体
Are now loaded with the pathogen
对准我国东海岸
And aimed at cities on our eastern seaboard.
你在虚张声势
You're bluffing.
为了表示诚意
As a sign of good faith,
我让您见识下  证明我并非虚张声势
I'm willing to show you that i'm... that i'm not bluffing.
看见了吗
You see that?
总统阁下
Madam president?
这就是你表示诚意的方式吗
You call this good faith?
你是要对自己国家开战啊  乔纳斯
You are waging war on your own country, Jonas.
当然了  我可不这么想
Well, of course, I wouldn't see it that way.
你到底想怎样
What do you want?
一会到了白宫我们再谈
Well, we can have that conversation a little later on at the White House.
你觉得我们能这么坐下来谈吗
You think we're going to just sit down and discuss this?
是的  就在您的总统办公室里
Yes i do, in the Oval Office,
我们私下谈  一个小时之内
In confidence, within the hour.
但同时  我觉得
But in the meantime, I think it is
美国人民不知道
To both of our advantage
你我相持不下的局面
That the American people do not know
对我们两个都有好处
The exact circumstance of this stand off.
所以您要对此次会晤守口如瓶
So you will keep this conversation to yourself,
并且召回战斗机
And turn the planes around.
您要是不答应的话  总统阁下
And if you don't comply, Madam President,
我就别无选择  只能发射那些导弹
I will have no choice but to launch those missiles.
霍奇斯先生
Mr. Hodges...
记住  你对我方的一举一动
And remember, i can detect any action you take
都在我的监视之下
Against our facility.
你有30秒
You have 30 seconds.
霍奇斯先生
Mr. Hodges...
Mr. Hodges!
史密斯上将  取消空袭
Abort the air strike, Admiral Smith.
总统阁下
Madam president...
照做就是了
Just do as I say.
阁下  恕我直言
Ma'am, with all respect...
见鬼  上将  马上取消空袭
Damn it, admiral, abort the air strike immediately!
我是史密斯上将
This is Admiral Smith.
总统有令  取消空袭
I have an abort order from the president.
战斗机取消攻击
Take fighters off target.
重复  战斗机取消攻击
Repeat. Take fighters off target.
等待确认
Stand by for confirmation.
[总统有令  取消空袭]
Executive order...Abort strike.
收到
Roger that.
攻击取消了  总统阁下
We're standing down, Madam President.